Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 4
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 4
- Box: 77, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 29: Strike action of Spanish workers, 1983; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 30: Union Break-through in Citibank, 1983; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 31: Unions examine links between retailing and banking, 1983; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 32: Unions examine links between retailing and banking, 1983; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 33: FIET Metro/Makro Company Council demands guarantee of trade union rights, 1983; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 34: International health and safety guidelines for White Collar Workers published, 1983; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 35: International Union meeting attacks job cuts in Rank Photocopy, 1983; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 36: International union critical of bank policies on technology and employment, 1984; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 37: FIET affiliates and IKEA managers discuss employment and working conditions at IKEA, 1984; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 38: International conference on trade union organisation of Professional and Managerial Staff, 1984; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 39: Limit visual display work says International Union Conference, 1984; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 40: Future of the Branch Network in banks, 1985; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 41: International Union study on cashless shopping published, 1985; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 42: International VDU guidelines published, 1985; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 43: International trade union conferences assemble representatives of three million bank and insurance workers, 1985; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 44: South Africa, 1985; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 45: FIET Company Council condemns Metro/Makro actions on South Africa and USA, 1985; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 46: FIET Company Council critical of IKEA management attitudes, 1985; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 47: FIET conference on personnel information systems to take place in Geneva, 28-29 November, 1985; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 48: Statement - the FIET-METRO/MAKRO Company Council, 1985; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 49: Unions call for international control over money laundering, 1986; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 50: White collar unions' policies for social recovery in Europe, 1986; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 51: International trade union leader calls for solidarity action with striking South African Commercial Workers, 1987; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 52: Strike at ok bazaars in South Africa, 1987; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 53: Latest Information on the ok Bazaars Strike, 1987; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 54: Trade unions in new initiatives to organise professional and managerial staff, 1987; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 55: Stock market crash reinforces trade union scepticism over privatisation of social welfare, 1987; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 56: Trade union concern over job prospects in European banking, 1987; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 57: Multi-national banks assailed for attacks on trade union rights, 1987; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 58: Banking trade unions criticise proposals of the EEC to liberalise banking laws in Europe, 1988; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 59: International trade union attacks labour relations practices of Japanese banks, 1988; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 60: FIET supports strike action by Greek bank workers, 1988; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 61: European agreement on vocational training in the retail trade sector, 1988; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 62: Infringements of trade union rights in banking underline the need for a social dimension to EEC directives, 1988; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 63: FIET to bring 'invisible people' into view, 1988; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 64: International support for strong unions in property services, 1989; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 65: Organising for tomorrow: FIET World Conference of Professional and Managerial Staff, 1989; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 66: FIET tackles multinational banks worldwide, 1989; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 67: Putting the social dialogue into practice, 1989; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 68: Unions concerned about the use of harmful chemicals in hairdressing, Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 69: Limits on shop opening hours and reduction in working hours features of new agreement in the German retail sector, 1989; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 70: Commercial workers call for a social Europe and express opposition to Sunday trading, 1989; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 71: Union recognition victory in us banking sector, 1990; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 72: The Trade union response to the financial services revolution, 1990; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 73: Hairdressers' health should not be threatened by secretiveness, 1990; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 74: Food Lion case sparks UFCW to file ILO complaint against US Government over freedom of association, 1990; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 75: Equal pay case brings pay increases for shop assistants in Great Britain, 1990; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 76: FIET appeals to foreign banks to respect trade union rights in Chile, 1990; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 77: Unfair labour practices in Pakistan, 1990; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 78: Global Commercial Workers' Summit concludes, 1990; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 79: International trade union solidarity proves key to unlocking ISS dispute, 1990; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 80: Salaried employees in industry express concern about upsurge of merger activity in Europe, 1990; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 81: FIET launches charter for hairdressers and beauticians, 1990; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 82: EURO-FIET Conference demands a social dimension to European integration, 1990; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 83: Report released on trade unions in East Europe, 1990; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 84: Single European market for insurance raising risks, 1991; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 85: Vulnerable banking sector faces sweeping job losses, 1991; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 86: EURO-FIET Executive Committee, 1991; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 87: European computer industry in a big squeeze - management is to blame, 1991; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 88: FIET protests Thai Junta's attacks on trade unions, 1991; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 89: World Bank again embroiled in privatisation pressure, 1991; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 90: 22nd FIET World Congress in San Francisco gives practicial, 1991; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 91: Improving the conditions of voluntary mobility controlling, 1991; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 92: Next annual session of the FIET Committee on Professional and Managerial Staff, 1991; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 93: FIET and Professional and Managerial Staff, 1991; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 94: Food Lion Sued, 1991; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 95: FIET calls for social dimension for MERCOSUR, 1991; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 96: Mobility of professional managerial staff in Europe, 1991; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 97: International union campaign against low pay in retail sector, 1991; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 98: Sunday trading, 1991; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 99: Professional and Managerial Staff expected to be more internationally, 1991; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 100: Urgent call for a social dimension to Mercosur, 1991; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 101: Bank union leaders question European Commission, 1992; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 102: FIET unions tackle the crisis in the African banking, 1992; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 103: European shop stewards in Aldi North get together, 1992; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 104: FIET organises international seminar for trade union representatives, 1992; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 105: 1st FIET property maintenance and security services world conference, 1992; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 106: First FIET World Conference for Property Services Workers, 1992; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 107: Trade Union Conference for professional and managerial staff, 1992; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 108: European Commerce Trade Unions draw up shopping list of multinationals, 1992; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 109: Insurance unions meet for the first time in Central and Eastern Europe, 1992; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 110: FIET bank unions express solidarity with trade unions in Central and Eastern Europe, 1992; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 111: Justice for janitors apple campaign bears fruit, 1992; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 112: Turkey: trade union rights in banking, 1992; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 113: FIET opens social dialogue with European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, 1992; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 114: Sunday trading in the United Kingdom, 1992; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 115: Guarding against another BCCI, 1992; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 116: FIET calls for a social dialogue in Delhaize le Lion, 1993; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 117: International trade union assembly for the Delhaize Group, 1993; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 118: Time to change? Euro-FIET women focus on working time issues, 1993; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 119: Zurich's strategy of social dumping to be raised in Swiss Parliament, 1993; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 120: EURO-FIET calls top European retailers to the negotiating table, 1993; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 121: Zurich Insurance exposed in the ILO and told to face the facts, 1993; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 122: Success at Zurich Insurance: UK Union MSF in recognition deal with Zurich, 1994; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 123: A "Formula for disaster"? Food Lion is still getting it wrong, 1994; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 124: FIET celebrates its 90th Anniversary, 1994; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 125: 7th Euro-FIET Conference: Jobs, Democracy and Dialogue, 1994; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 126: ILO sets new work programme for salaried employees and professional workers, 1994; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 127: June 15: International Justice Day, Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Item 128: 3rd FIET World Conference for Professional and Managerial Staff, 1994; Publication (Box 77, Folder 14)
- Box: 77, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Report of the 7th ISETU/FIET Congress: Geneva, 19-21 October 1988, Publication (Box 77, Folder 15)
    Author: ISETU/FIET Congress
  - Item 2: 7th ISETU/FIET Congress: Challenges without frontiers, 1988; Publication (Box 77, Folder 15)
- Box: 77, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: l'employe: dans le monde du travail libre, 1969; Publication (Box 77, Folder 16)
    Author: Federation internationale des employes et des techniciens
    Notes: Janv-Fevr no.18
  - Item 2: l'employe: dans le monde du travail libre, 1969; Publication (Box 77, Folder 16)
    Notes: Juillet-aout no.16
  - Item 3: l'employe: dans le monde du travail libre, 1968; Publication (Box 77, Folder 16)
    Notes: fevrier no.11
  - Item 4: the non-manual worker, 1969; Publication (Box 77, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.19
  - Item 5: the non-manual worker, 1968; Publication (Box 77, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.17
  - Item 6: the non-manual worker, 1968; Publication (Box 77, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.15
  - Item 7: the non-manual worker, 1968; Publication (Box 77, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.14
  - Item 8: the non-manual worker, 1968; Publication (Box 77, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.13
  - Item 9: the non-manual worker, 1968; Publication (Box 77, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.12
  - Item 10: the non-manual worker, 1968; Publication (Box 77, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.11
- Box: 77, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: the non-manual worker, 1969; Publication (Box 77, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.20
  - Item 2: the non-manual worker, 1967; Publication (Box 77, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.9
  - Item 3: the non-manual worker, 1967; Publication (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: the non-manual worker, 1966; Publication (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: the non-manual worker, 1966; Publication (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: the non-manual worker, 1966; Publication (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: the non-manual worker, 1966; Publication (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: the non-manual worker, 1966; Publication (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Item 9: the non-manual worker, 1966; Publication (Box 77, Folder 17)
- Box: 77, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Constitution as revised by the Tenth World Congress ( Vienna, July 1972), Publication (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Constitution as adopted by the 14th World Congress Marseille-France-, 1985; Publication (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Constitution as adopted by the 14th World Congress Marseille-France-, 1985; Publication (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Constitution as adopted by the 14th World Congress Marseille-France-, 1985; Publication (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Constitution as adopted by the 14th World Congress Marseille-France-, 1985; Publication (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Constitution, 1972; Publication (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Constitution, 1989; Publication (Box 77, Folder 18)
- Box: 77, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: L'Educateur Syndicaliste, 1989; Publication (Box 77, Folder 19)
    Notes: 15
  - Item 2: L'Educateur Syndicaliste, 1988; Publication (Box 77, Folder 19)
    Notes: fevrier
  - Item 3: L'Educateur Syndicaliste, 1987; Publication (Box 77, Folder 19)
    Notes: novembre
  - Item 4: Trabajadores de la educacion, 1989; Publication (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: Trabajadores de la educacion, 1988; Publication (Box 77, Folder 19)
    Notes: febrero
  - Item 6: Workers in education, 1987; Publication (Box 77, Folder 19)
    Notes: November
  - Item 7: Workers in education, 1987; Publication (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Item 8: Workers in education, 1988; Publication (Box 77, Folder 19)
    Notes: February
  - Item 9: Workers in education, 1989; Publication (Box 77, Folder 19)
    Notes: June-Sept
- Box: 77, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Trentieme Anniversaire de la Fise: 1946-1976, Publication (Box 77, Folder 20)
    Author: Federation internationale de la FISE
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1982; Publication (Box 77, Folder 20)
    Author: International Federation of Plantation, Agricultural and Allied Workers
  - Item 3: Constitution, 1982; Publication (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: Constitution, 1976; Publication (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Item 5: IFPAAW: the official organ of the International Federation of Plantation, Agricultural and Allied Workers, 1964; Publication (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Item 6: IFPAAW: the official organ of the International Federation of Plantation, Agricultural and Allied Workers, 1965; Publication (Box 77, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.10
  - Item 7: IFPAAW: the official organ of the International Federation of Plantation, Agricultural and Allied Workers, 1970; Publication (Box 77, Folder 20)
- Box: 77, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: IFPAAW: the official organ of the International Federation of Plantation, Agricultural and Allied Workers, 1960; Publication (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: IFPAAW: the official organ of the International Federation of Plantation, Agricultural and Allied Workers, 1963; Publication (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: IFPAAW: the official organ of the International Federation of Plantation, Agricultural and Allied Workers, 1962; Publication (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: Constitution, 1982; Publication (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: Constitution, 1982; Publication (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Item 6: Constitution, 1988; Publication (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Item 7: IFPAAW snips, 1980; Publication (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Item 8: IFPAAW snips, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Item 9: Circular letter no. 12, 1976; Publication (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Item 10: Circular letter no. 12, 1976; Publication (Box 77, Folder 21)
- Box: 77, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Statutes, 1992; Publication (Box 77, Folder 22)
    Author: International Graphical Federation
  - Item 2: Statistics, 1976; Publication (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Alliance Graphique Internationale: List of members, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 22)
    Author: Alliance Graphique Internationale
  - Item 4: Statutes: igf-fgi, 1988; Publication (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Item 5: Statutes: igf-fgi, 1992; Publication (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Item 6: Statutes: igf-fgi, 1985; Publication (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Item 7: Statutes: igf-fgi, 1988; Publication (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Item 8: Statuten = Statutes = Statuts = Stadgar, 1979; Publication (Box 77, Folder 22)
    Language: German; English; French; Danish.
  - Item 9: Statutes 1977, Publication (Box 77, Folder 22)
    Author: Alliance graphique internationale
  - Item 10: Statutes 1977, Publication (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Item 11: Introducing the International Graphical Federation, Publication (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Item 12: Introducing the International Graphical Federation, Publication (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Item 13: International Graphical Federation, Publication (Box 77, Folder 22)
- Box: 77, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: 8th IMF World Shipbuilding Conference, 27-29 November 1979, Publication (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: Report of IMF mission to Poland, 3-11 December 1980, 1981; Publication (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: IMF activities for shipyard workers in an adverse economic environment, 1979; Publication (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Item 4: Wages, working and social conditions in the world shipbuilding industry, 1979; Publication (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Item 5: Workers and the world shipbuilding crisis, 1979; Publication (Box 77, Folder 23)
- Box: 78, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: IMF Press Release: International Union condemns South African shooting, 1985; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: IMF Press Release: International Union condemns South African shooting, 1985; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Rules, 1977; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: 25th IMF World Congress, Washington, D.C., USA, May 24-29, 1981: resolutions and statements, Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: 25th IMF World Congress, Washington, D.C., USA, May 24-29, 1981: resolutions and statements, Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: 25th IMF World Congress, Washington, D.C., USA, May 24-29, 1981: resolutions and statements, Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Resolutions, 24th IMF World Congress: Munich, 24-28 October 1977, Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Resolutions, 24th IMF World Congress: Munich, 24-28 October 1977, Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Resolutions, 24th IMF World Congress: Munich, 24-28 October 1977, Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Asbestos, 1984; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Asbestos, 1984; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Asbestos, 1984; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Asbestos, 1984; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Eccentric presses, 1984; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Eccentric presses, 1984; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Welding work, 1985; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Welding work, 1985; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Lead, 1984; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Lift and carry properly, 1985; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: Lift and carry properly, 1985; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: Lift and carry properly, 1985; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: Occupational skin diseases, 1986; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: Occupational skin diseases, 1986; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 24: Occupational skin diseases, 1986; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: Paints varnishes glues, 1987; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 26: Paints varnishes glues, 1987; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Item 27: Sedentary work, 1988; Publication (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Box: 78, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report to the Central Committee: General Electric Workers' World Coordination, Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Enquiry on total wage costs in the Shipbuilding Industry: submitted to Delegates to the Asian/European Shipbuilding Seminar, June 2-4, 1986, Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: IMF affiliates in OECD Member Countries, 1976; Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: International Solidarity of Ford Workers, 1971; Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Agenda: Joint-meeting of IMF World Auto Councils: T.U.C. Congress House, Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Guidelines for a code of behaviour: first steps towards, social and economic control measures on multinational companies, 1976; Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Latest Ford offer, basis for settlement subject to ratification, 1971; Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Moving from GAAP; Joseph P. Cummings - Tomorrow: omnicenters on the landscape?; Lathrop Douglas - Union's expanding international coordination; Burton Bendiner - Contracting for an employee counseling service; Cavin P. Leeman, 1974; Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: IMF News -, 1976; Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: IMF News -, 1976; Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.10/11
  - Item 11: IMF News -, 1976; Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.22
  - Item 12: Orienteringsverslag voor het 19e congres van het W.V.A. in De Haan aan Zee, Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
    Language: Dutch.
  - Item 13: Observations on some of the worldwide economic issues of the coming year, 1977; Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
    Author: Wassily Leontief
  - Item 14: International Division of Labour: present state and proposed reforms: paper prepared for IMF, Geneva, 1977; Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
    Author: Christel Bergmann
  - Item 15: The IMF World Auto Councils: auto workers meet the global challenge of the multinational auto companies, Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: IMF Nissan and Toyota World Auto Councils: Third meeting: Jidosha Roren Education Center, Gotemba, Japan, September 12-13, 1977, Publication (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Box: 78, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Remarks by Herman Rebhan, 1982; Publication (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Minutes of the Central Committee Meeting, Madrid, Spain, June 9-10, 1988, Publication (Box 78, Folder 3)